BE CAREFUL WHAT YOU WISH FOR... IT JUST MIGHT COME TRUE.
Truly Madly Deeply is a fantasy, drama, comedy
film directed by Anthony Minghella.
Nina is totally heartbroken at the death of her boyfriend Jamie, but
is even more unprepared for his return as a ghost.
At first it's almost as good as it used to be – hey, even the
rats that infested her house have disappeared.
But Jamie starts bringing ghostly friends home and behaving more and more oddly.
Nina, played by Juliet Stevenson.
Jamie, played by Alan Rickman.
Mark, played by Michael Maloney.
Sandy, played by Bill Paterson.
Titus, played by Christopher Rozycki.
George, played by David Ryall.
Truly, Madly, Deeply is a 1990 British fantasy drama film made for the BBC's
Screen Two series, by BBC Films, Lionheart and Winston Pictures.
The film, written and directed by Anthony Minghella,
stars Juliet Stevenson and Alan Rickman.
The film explores themes of london, england, river
thames, afterlife, cello, love.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.